# **Abhimanyu Kumar**

dmads.abhimanyu@gmail.com 9950477937 house no. 3,shri shankar nagar,near judicial academy,Jhalamand Jodhpur, Rajasthan

## Summary

Web Developer with 5 years practice in web development using php programming language. Possesses an updated working knowledge of different web and mobile technologies. Capable of establishing, organising and prioritising workloads and tasks in a collaborative and team setting.

## Experience

# **PHP Developer**

NBN MINDS • jodhpur, Rajasthan 05/2019 - Present

# **PHP Developer**

Dheer Software Solutions • Jodhpur, Rajasthan 02/2018 - 04/2019

# **PHP Developer**

Harsh Technology • Jodhpur, Rajasthan 03/2016 - 01/2018

CSS

#### **Skills**

- HTML
- Jquerylaravel
- Core php Zend

#### **Education**

# **BCA**

Aishwarya College of Education • Jodhpur, Rajasthan

12/2013

• Currently completing courses in computer science

# **MCA**

Sikkim Manipal University • Jodhpur, Rajasthan

01/2017

## Languages

Hindi
normal english